<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="62">
	<author>Jason06 / Glowins Modschmiede</author>
	<version>2.9.2.1</version>
	<title>
		<en>Headland Management</en>
		<de>Vorgewende Management</de>
		<fr>Gestion Des Promontoires</fr>
		<cz>Souvraťový Management</cz>
    </title>
    <description>
		<en>
<![CDATA[
Headland management for tractors, field sprayers, mowers and harvesters.

With headland management, functions of vehicles can be combined and activated together at the touch of a button to simplify turning manoeuvres when working in the field. All functions can be activated and deactivated individually for each vehicle via a GUI to achieve ideal adaptation to the work being carried out.

The headland management system must be added once to the respective vehicle in the shop or in the workshop as a configuration before it can be used. The cost for this is 3000,-.
It can be activated and deactivated in the vehicle with Shift-X. Alternatively, different buttons for activation and deactivation can be configured. The GUI is called up by default with Shift+Ctrl+X.

Included functions:
- Reduce speed (cruise control) and raise again, reactivate cruise control if previously active
- Raise lowered implements and lower them again
- Turn plough, single-stage or two-stage (via centre position)
- Raise and change ridge markers
- Control crab steering
- Disengage and re-engage power take-off(s) and hydraulics
- Beep when headland management is activated

If VCA Mod (FS22_VehicleControlAddon) is present:
- Deactivate and reactivate GPS track guidance
- Disengage and re-engage active differential locks
- Trigger VCA's turn function

If Guidance Steering (FS22_guidanceSteering) is present: 
- Deactivate and reactivate GPS guidance
- Headland automatic: Activate headland management automatically when headland is reached

Prepared and provided with one of the following updates when SpeedControl Mod (FS22_zzzSpeedControl) is available:
- Speed adjustment also possible by changing the cruise control level

Further ideas or wishes are welcome at https://github.com/jason0611/FS22_HeadlandManagement

ChangeLog V2.0.0.0:
- Ready for Farming Simulator 22
- Many thanks to Kynuska for the czech translation

And many thanks to team Agrarplay and the project LU Wohnzimmer for the extensive test-support!

]]>
		</en>	
		<de>
<![CDATA[
Vorgewende-Management für Schlepper, Feldspritzen, Mäher und Erntemaschinen

Mit dem Vorgewende-Management können Funktionen im Fahrzeug zusammengefasst und gemeinsam per Knopfdruck aktiviert werden, um Wendemanöver bei der Feldarbeit zu vereinfachen. Alle Funktionen sind je Fahrzeug über eine GUI einzeln aktivierbar und deaktivierbar, um eine ideale Anpassung an die durchgeführten Arbeiten zu erreichen.

Das Vorgewende-Management muss vor der Nutzung im Shop oder in der Werkstatt dem jeweiligen Fahrzeug einmalig als Konfiguration hinzugefügt werden. Die Kosten dafür liegen bei 3000,-. 
Es kann im Fahrzeug mit (links) Shift-X aktiviert und deaktiviert werden. Es lassen sich auch verschiedene Tasten für Aktivierung und Deaktivierung konfigurieren. Die GUI wird standardmäßig mit Shift+Strg+X aufgerufen.

Enthaltene Funktionen:
- Geschwindigkeit (Tempomat) reduzieren und wieder anheben, Tempomat reaktivieren, falls er vorher aktiv war
- Abgesenkte Geräte ausheben und wieder absenken
- Pflug drehen, einstufig oder zweistufig (über die Mittelstellung)
- Spurreisser ausheben und wechseln
- Seitenwechsel bei aktiviertem Hundegang
- Zapfwelle(n) und Hydraulik abschalten und wieder anschalten
- Hinweiston bei aktiviertem Vorgewendemanagement

Bei vorhandenem VCA Mod (FS22_VehicleControlAddon):
- GPS Spurführung deaktivieren und reaktivieren
- Aktive Differentialsperren lösen und wieder setzen
- Auslösen der Wendefunktion

Bei vorhandenem Guidance Steering (FS22_guidanceSteering):
- GPS Spurführung deaktivieren und reaktivieren
- Vorgewendeautomatik: Automatische Aktivierung des Vorgewendemanagements, wenn das Vorgewende erreicht wird

Vorbereitet und mit einem der folgenden Updates bereitgestellt, sobald SpeedControl (FS22_zzzSpeedControl?) verfügbar ist:
- Geschwindigkeitsanpassung auch über Wechsel der Tempomatstufe möglich

Weitere Ideen oder Wünsche werden gerne unter https://github.com/jason0611/FS22_HeadlandManagement entgegengenommen

ChangeLog V2.0.0.0:
- Bereit für den Landwirtschaftssimulator 22
- Vielen Dank an Kynuska für die tschechische Übersetzung

Vielen Dank auch an das Team Agrarplay und das Projekt LU Wohnzimmer für die umfangreiche Testunterstützung!

]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
<![CDATA[
Gestion des fourrières pour tracteurs, pulvérisateurs, faucheuses et moissonneuses.

Grâce à la gestion des manœuvres en bout de champ, les fonctions peuvent être combinées dans le véhicule et activées ensemble par simple pression sur un bouton afin de simplifier les manœuvres de virage lors des travaux dans les champs. Toutes les fonctions peuvent être activées et désactivées individuellement pour chaque véhicule via une interface graphique afin de s'adapter parfaitement au travail effectué.

Le système de gestion des manœuvres en bout de champ doit être ajouté une fois au véhicule concerné en tant que configuration avant de pouvoir être utilisé dans le magasin ou dans l'atelier. Le coût de cette opération est de 3 000 euros.
Il peut être activé et désactivé dans le véhicule avec le levier de vitesse (gauche) Shift-X. Boutons différents peuvent également être configurés pour l'activation et la désactivation. L'interface graphique est appelée par défaut avec Shift+Ctrl+X.

Fonctions incluses :
- Réduire la vitesse (régulateur de vitesse) et remonter, réactiver le régulateur de vitesse s'il était précédemment actif.
- Relever les outils abaissés et les abaisser à nouveau.
- Charrue de retournement, à une ou deux étapes (via la position centrale)
- Relever et changer les rippers de voie
- Changement de côté avec la marche en crabe activée
- Désengager et réengager la ou les prises de force et le système hydraulique.
- Bip lorsque la gestion des tournières est activée

Si le VCA Mod (FS22_VehicleControlAddon) est présent :
- Désactiver et réactiver le guidage par trace GPS
- Désengager et réengager les blocages de différentiel actif
- Déclenchement de la fonction de retournement

Si la fonction Guidance Steering (FS22_guidanceSteering) est présente : 
- Désactiver et réactiver le guidage GPS
- Gestion automatique des tournières : activation automatique de la gestion des tournières lorsque la tournière est atteinte

Préparé et mis à disposition avec l'une des mises à jour suivantes, dès que SpeedControl (FS22_zzzSpeedControl ?) sera disponible :
- Réglage de la vitesse également possible en modifiant le niveau du régulateur de vitesse.

D'autres idées ou souhaits sont les bienvenus à l'adresse https://github.com/jason0611/FS19_HeadlandManagement, veuillez écrire en allemand ou en anglais

Changelog V2.0.0.0:
- Prêt pour le FS22
- Merci beaucoup à Kynuska pour la traduction en tchèque

Un grand merci à l'équipe d'Agrarplay et au projet LU Wohnzimmer pour leur soutien important en matière de tests !

]]>
		</fr>
		<cz>
<![CDATA[
Správa souvratí pro traktory, polní postřikovače, sekačky a kombajny.

Díky řízení na souvrati lze funkce vozidel kombinovat a aktivovat společně stisknutím tlačítka pro zjednodušení manévrů při otáčení při práci na poli. Všechny funkce lze aktivovat a deaktivovat individuálně pro každé vozidlo prostřednictvím grafického uživatelského rozhraní, aby bylo dosaženo ideálního přizpůsobení prováděné práci.

Systém souvraťového managementu musí být před použitím jednou přidán do příslušného vozidla v obchodě nebo v dílně jako konfigurace. Cena za to je 3000 €.
Ve vozidle ji lze aktivovat a deaktivovat pomocí Shift-X. Alternativně lze nakonfigurovat různá tlačítka pro aktivaci a deaktivaci. Nastavení se standardně vyvolává pomocí Shift+Ctrl+X.

Zahrnuté funkce:
- Snížení rychlosti (tempomatu) a opakovaná aktivace, pokud byl dříve aktivní
- Zvednutí nářadí a opětovné spuštění
- Otočení pluhu, v jednom nebo dvou krocích (přes středovou polohu)
- Zvednutí a výměna znamenáků
- Ovládání krabího řízení
- Odpojení a zpětné zapojení diferenciálu(ů) a hydraulik
- Možnost zvukové signalizace při aktivním otáčení na souvrati

Pokud je přítomen VCA Mod (FS22_VehicleControlAddon):
- Deaktivuje a opětovně aktivuje naváděnou trasu GPS
- Vypne a znovu zapne uzávěrky diferenciálů
- Spusťí vloženou funkci otáčení VCA

Připraveno a poskytnuto s jednou z následujících aktualizací, když bude k dispozici navádění řízení (FS22_guidanceSteering?):
- Deaktivuje a znovu aktivuje navádění GPS
- Souvraťová automatika: Aktivace souvraťového řízení automaticky při dosažení souvrati

Připraveno a poskytnuto s jednou z následujících aktualizací, když bude k dispozici SpeedControl Mod (FS22_zzzSpeedControl):
- Nastaví rychlost dle úrovní tempomatu

Další nápady nebo přání jsou vítány na https://github.com/jason0611/FS22_HeadlandManagement

ChangeLog V2.0.0.0:
- Připraveno pro Farming Simulator 22
- Děkujeme Kynuskovi za český překlad

Mnohokrát děkujeme týmu Agrarplay a projektu LU Wohnzimmer za rozsáhlou testovací podporu!

]]>
		</cz>
	    
 	</description>	
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
    	<sourceFile filename="headlandManagementRegister.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
	<actions>
		<action name="HLM_TOGGLESTATE" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_SWITCHOFF" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_SWITCHON" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_SHOWGUI" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
	</actions>
	<inputBinding>	
		<actionBinding action="HLM_TOGGLESTATE">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_x" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="HLM_SHOWGUI">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_lctrl KEY_x" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>
</modDesc>
